<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>interview-topics on Java Principal</title>
    <link>https://akhilesh006.github.io/javaprincipal/tags/interview-topics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in interview-topics on Java Principal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 19:29:13 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://akhilesh006.github.io/javaprincipal/tags/interview-topics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Interview Preparation</title>
      <link>https://akhilesh006.github.io/javaprincipal/posts/java/interview-prep-topics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 19:29:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akhilesh006.github.io/javaprincipal/posts/java/interview-prep-topics/</guid>
      <description>Tech Interview Preparation Following are the best posts of Leetcode platform on data-structure and algorithms.
 DP for beginners by @wh0ami  LIST   Graph for beginners by @wh0ami  LIST   Sliding window for beginners by @wh0ami  LIST   DP Patterns by @aatalyk Leetcode patterns from edu_cative_dot_io by @late_riser List of questions sorted by common patterns by @Maverick2594 How to solve DP - String? Template and 4 Steps to be followed by @igooglethings Using bit manipulation to solve problems easily and efficiently by @LHearen Recursive approach to segment trees and range sum queries and lazy propagation How to use Leetcode efficiently and effectively by beginners by @megaspazz Dynamic Programming Questions thread by @karansingh1559 DP Classification helpful notes by @adityakrverma Comprehensive Data Structure and Algorithm Study Guide by @xrssa Backtracking Summary and general template to solve many problems by @dichen001 How to approach DP problems by @heroes3001 A general approach to backtracking questions by @issac3 Top 75 Leetcode questions for interview preparation curated by Blind Topic wise problems for beginners by @yashrsharma44 Sliding Window algorithm template to solve all the Leetcode substring search problem by @chaoyanghe Greedy for beginners by @wh0ami  LIST   From-good-to-great.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>